<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<cml tuio="false" simulator="true">

  <Stage fullscreen="true"/>

  <LibraryKit>
    <Library type="swf" src="library/swfs/openexhibits_assets.swf"/>
  </LibraryKit>

  <Background color="0XFF00FF">
    <Graphic shape="rectangle" width="1920" height="1080" fill="color" color="0x000000" lineStroke="0" alpha="1"/>
  </Background>


  <Album x="20" y="120" margin="20" width="1880" height="890" backgroundAlpha="0" mouseChildren="true" clusterBubbling="true" dragGesture="album-drag">


    <RenderKit dataRootTag="museum">
      <Renderer>
        <TouchContainer width="640" height="1050" mouseChildren="true" fill="color" color="0x000000">
          <Graphic shape="rectangle" width="640" height="1050" fill="color" color="0x320000" lineStroke="0" alpha="1"/>
          <TouchContainer mouseChildren="false" targetParent="true">
            <Image src="{    imagepath    }" width="640" height="500"/>
          </TouchContainer>
          <TouchContainer mouseChildren="false" targetParent="true">
            <Text text="{    title    }" y="520" textAlign="center" color="0xfafcfb" fontSize="30" width="640" font="OpenSansBold" selectable="false"/>
            <Text text="{    location    }" y="580" textAlign="center" color="0x9a9c9b" fontSize="30" width="640" font="OpenSansBold" selectable="false"/>
            <Text text="{    year    }" y="620" textAlign="center" color="0xdcdedd" fontSize="70" width="640" font="OpenSansRegular" selectable="false"/>
            <Text text="{    excerpt    }" x="20" y="730" selectable="false" color="0xe0e0dc" fontSize="20" wordWrap="true" multiline="true" width="600" height="300" font="OpenSansRegular"/>
            <Text text="{    citation - back    }" y="980" x="20" wordWrap="true" textAlign="center" color="0xbbbb91" fontSize="14" width="500" font="OpenSansRegular" selectable="false"/>
          </TouchContainer>
          <Button id="info-btn" class="info_btn" dispatch="{    button - dispatch    }" hit="info-hit" initial="info-up" down="info-down" up="info-up" out="info-up" x="580" y="980">
            <Container id="info-up">
              <Graphic alpha="0.5" shape="circle" radius="20" lineStroke="0" color="0x0000FF"/>
              <SWF alpha="1" x="15" y="8" color="0xFFFFFF" scale="1.6" classRef="org.openexhibits.assets.Info"/>
            </Container>
            <Container id="info-down">
              <Graphic id="info-bg-down" shape="circle" radius="20" lineStroke="0" color="0x474747"/>
              <SWF alpha="0.5" x="15" y="8" color="0x000000" scale="1.6" classRef="org.openexhibits.assets.Info"/>
            </Container>
            <Container id="info-hit" alpha="0">
              <Graphic id="info-bg-down" shape="circle" radius="20" lineStroke="0" color="0x666666"/>
            </Container>
          </Button>

          <TouchContainer id="{    panel - id    }" mouseChildren="true" visible="false">
            <Graphic visible="true" shape="rectangle" width="640" height="1050" fill="color" color="0x54482b" lineStroke="0" alpha="1" mouseChildren="false">
              <Image src="{    imagepath - 2    }" width="640" height="500"/>
              <Text id="txt1" text="{    museum - text    }" x="20" y="540" width="600" height="860" color="0xffffff" wordWrap="true" multiline="true" fontSize="20" font="OpenSansRegular"/>

              <Text text="{    citation - front    }" y="980" x="20" wordWrap="true" textAlign="center" color="0xbbbb91" fontSize="14" width="500" font="OpenSansRegular" selectable="false"/>

            </Graphic>
            <Button x="600" y="20" class="close_btn" dispatch="{    button - dispatch    }" hit="close-hit" initial="close-up" down="close-down" up="close-up" out="close-up" scale="0.75">
              <Container id="close-up" class="up">
                <Graphic alpha="1" shape="circle" radius="20" lineStroke="0" color="0xffffff"/>
                <SWF alpha="1" x="11" y="11" color="0x000000" scale="1.6" ref="org.openexhibits.assets.Close"/>
              </Container>
              <Container id="close-down" class="down">
                <Graphic alpha="1" shape="circle" radius="20" lineStroke="0" color="0x000000"/>
                <SWF alpha="1" x="11" y="11" color="0x000000" scale="1.6" ref="org.openexhibits.assets.Close"/>
              </Container>
              <Container id="close-hit" class="hit">
                <Graphic id="close-hit-bg" shape="circle" radius="20" alpha="0"/>
              </Container>
            </Button>
          </TouchContainer>
        </TouchContainer>
      </Renderer>

      <RendererData>
        <!-- <museum /> elements here -->
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:southend</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>southend</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref774001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/BC1986019ref484001.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>Boston College in the South End</title>
          <location>Boston, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>The first Boston College buildings were completed in Boston's South End neighborhood in 1860, but there were not enough Jesuits available locally to staff a college. The buildings were then used as a seminary. John Bapst, S.J. and Robert Fulton, S.J., respectively the first president and dean of Boston College, were both assigned there.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>Boston College was incorporated in 1863, and admitted 23 students in September, 1864. The earliest students ranged in age from 10-20, and followed a curriculum designed to take 7 years to complete. BC's first class graduated in 1877.</museum-text>
          <citation>Boston College South End campus exterior, from Boston College building and campus images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>Football team, 1897, from Boston College athletics photographs (BC.1986.019), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:immaculateconception</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>immaculateconception</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref623001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/BC19870120684.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>Church of Immaculate Conception</title>
          <location>Boston, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>Bishop John Bernard Fitzpatrick laid the structure's cornerstone in 1858, and The Church of the Immaculate Conception was dedicated in 1861. Its first pastor was Boston College founder John McElroy, SJ. Electric light was added in a renovation in 1895, and two side chapels were added in 1901.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>The Church helped create a sense of community for Boston College faculty and students and the surrounding area. Catholic students were required to attended Mass every morning at 8:30, and school was in session from Monday through Saturday.</museum-text>
          <citation>Immaculate Conception Church, circa 1860, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>Immaculate Conception Church altar during the Boston College High School centennial, 1964, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:chestnuthill</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>chestnuthill</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref506001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/BC1987012ref576001.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>Building a Campus in Chestnut Hill</title>
          <location>Chestnut Hill, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>The iconic Recitation Hall, informally called the Tower Building, was later named Gasson Hall, after Thomas I. Gasson, SJ, the Boston College President who brought the campus to Chestnut Hill. Architectural firm Maginnis &amp; Walsh's design of this and other early buildings on the new campus helped popularize the Collegiate Gothic style across many college campuses in the early 20th century.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>The student magazine Stylus was founded in 1883, and, once the College moved to Chestnut Hill, its office was in Gasson Hall. The paper featured literary contributions, as well as alumni, athletics, and other college news. By 1933, the Stylus was entirely an undergraduate literary magazine; it continues as such today.</museum-text>
          <citation>Gasson Hall, Clifton Church, photographer, 1918, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>Gasson Hall, Stylus office, 1916, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:stmarys</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>stmarys</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref943001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/bc0000216.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>St. Mary's Hall</title>
          <location>Chestnut Hill, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>The second building on the Chestnut Hill campus, St. Mary's was built to house the Jesuit community and continues to provide living quarters and amenities for them to this day. It was most recently renovated in 2015 to include a classroom and administrative space for the Woods College of Advancing Studies.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>The St. Mary's Hall Chapel is one of several spaces on campus which offers Boston College students, faculty, and staff a place for worship, reflection, and private prayer.</museum-text>
          <citation>Saint Mary's Hall from unpaved Linden Lane, Clifton Church, photographer, undated, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>Raychel Brown praying in St. Mary's Chapel at the all-day vigil for peace in the Persian Gulf, Geoff Why, photographer, 1991, from Boston College photographs (BC.2002.025), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:sciencebuilding</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>sciencebuilding</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref1547001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/BC1987012ref333001.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>The Science Building</title>
          <location>Chestnut Hill, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>The Science Building's architects, Maginnis &amp; Walsh, studied the facilities of MIT, Harvard, and Yale to create an efficient design for the building that would house the biology, physics, and chemistry departments. The building was completed in 1924. Maginnis &amp; Walsh was awarded the J. Harleston Parker Medal by the Boston Society of Architects, for the most beautiful structure in Greater Boston. The Science Building is now named for William J. Devlin, SJ, BC's 15th President.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>Devlin Hall was designed to include classroom and lab space for 1,000 students, along with an extensive collection of biological specimens, an electric generator room, and machine shops.</museum-text>
          <citation>Devlin Hall postcard, Clifton Church, photographer, undated, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>Devlin Hall biology lab, undated, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:library</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>library</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref1511001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/BC1987012ref180001.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>The Library</title>
          <location>Chestnut Hill, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>The Library - later named for BC's first president, John Bapst, SJ - was the fourth building on the Chestnut Hill campus and was its main library from 1925 to 1984. It contributes to the iconic BC skyline with its distinctive Margaret Elizabeth Ford Memorial Tower. Since the mid 1980s, the John J. Burns Library, which houses the university's special collections and its University Archives, occupies the building's north wing.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>While the Bapst Library's focus changed after the opening of O'Neill Library in 1984, its iconic study space, Gargan Hall, retains its original appearance and purpose. The library is now the home of art, architecture, museum studies, and photography collections. It is a favorite stop on campus tours and is frequently included on lists of the most beautiful college libraries.</museum-text>
          <citation>Bapst Library Ford Tower from Linden Lane, Clifton Church, photographer, undated, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>Bapst Library Gargan Hall, circa 1952, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:alumnifield</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>alumnifield</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref8001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/BC1987012ref18003.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>Alumni Field</title>
          <location>Chestnut Hill, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>Although track and baseball were played by students in the 1870s, and a football team was officially recognized in 1893, lack of practice and playing grounds remained a problem. After the move to Chestnut Hill, the long-planned-for athletic field, "Alumni Field," was opened in 1915. Even then, to accommodate crowds the team often played their home games at larger area football fields, including Fenway Park and Braves Field.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>Alumni Field was enjoyed by students through all seasons. After the new &amp;ldquo;Alumni Stadium&amp;rdquo; was a built and dedicated in 1957, a section of the former Alumni Field became known as &amp;ldquo;the Dust Bowl.&amp;rdquo; McElroy and Stokes Halls as well as the campus green (Stokes' lawn) occupy the space today.</museum-text>
          <citation>Alumni Field renovation, circa 1932, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>Alumni Field as hockey and ice rink, 1920s, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:cushinig</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>cushing</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref287001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/BC1988027ref164001.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>Cushing Hall</title>
          <location>Chestnut Hill, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>The nursing school, founded in 1947 and originally located at the Intown campus on Newbury Street. Richard Cardinal Cushing was instrumental in raising funds for the construction of a new building on the Chestnut Hill campus for the school, which moved in 1960. The building was named after Cushing.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>Boston College nurses are welcomed to the profession with a pinning ceremony, where faculty present pins to each member of the graduating class.</museum-text>
          <citation>Cushing Hall main entrance, 1960, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>School of Nursing pinning ceremony, 1965, from Boston College commencement materials (BC.1988.027), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:mcguinn</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>mcguinn</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref683001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/bc0000447.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>McGuinn Hall</title>
          <location>Chestnut Hill, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>In 1968, the School of Social Work moved to a newly constructed Chestnut Hill building. Named for Walter McGuinn, SJ, the co-founder and first dean of the School of Social Work, the building housed the social sciences.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>Classes at Boston College's School of Social Work were first held at 126 Newbury Street, Boston College's Intown campus, which also accommodated the Schools of Business Administration and Nursing and the &amp;ldquo;Intown College,&amp;rdquo; precursor to the Woods College of Advancing Studies.</museum-text>
          <citation>McGuinn Hall dedication, circa 1968, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>Boston College School of Social Work, Class of 1953, from Boston College photographs, John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
        <museum>
          <button-dispatch>down:oneill</button-dispatch>
          <panel-id>oneill</panel-id>
          <imagepath>library/images/BC1987012ref788001.jpg</imagepath>
          <imagepath-2>library/images/BC1987012ref829001.jpg</imagepath-2>
          <title>O'Neill Library</title>
          <location>Chestnut Hill, MA</location>
          <year/>
          <excerpt>Dedicated in 1984 and named for Thomas P. "Tip" O'Neill, Jr., Boston College alumnus ('36), former Massachusetts Congressman, and Speaker of the United States House of Representatives, O'Neill Library was designed to meet the expanding research and collections needs of Boston College.</excerpt>
          <museum-text>The main research library on campus, O'Neill is central to the Boston College Libraries' mission to acquire, preserve, and facilitate access to world-class collections, engage in collaborations that benefit scholarship, teaching, and learning, and support student formation. O'Neill provides dynamic user space, collections, and services that anticipate the evolving needs of diverse communities.</museum-text>
          <citation>O'Neill Library, 1984, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation>
          <citation-back>O'Neill Library, 1988, from Boston College Building and Campus Images (BC.1987.012), John J. Burns Library, Boston College.</citation-back>
        </museum>
      </RendererData>

    </RenderKit>

  </Album>

</cml>
